Seyfarth Shaw Labor Publications 6346 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw Labor Publications
1949-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw LLP
6346 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Publications.
7850711
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Publications; Shaw, Seyfarth
7850711
- AFL-CIO General, 1963-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  magazine articles, news clippings
  - Item 1: Trade Adjustment: The New Realism, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 1962
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: This is the AFL-CIO, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: January 1966
  - Item 3: The Export of American Jobs, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Andrew J. Biemiller
    Notes: May 19, 1970
  - Item 4: The National Economy 1973, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Power- for What?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: George Meany
  - Item 6: Labor's Key Role in Workplace Training, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Markley Roberts and Robert Wozniak
    Notes: September 1994
  - Item 7: The Decline of the AFL-CIO, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Frank J. Donner
    Notes: August 30, 1962
  - Item 8: The House of Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Circular no. 205: A-12, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 10/19/1962
  - Item 10: Reuther Ties Riots to Meany, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Martin Arundel
    Notes: 8/13/1967
  - Item 11: The AFL-CIO's Inner Struggle, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Newsweek
    Notes: December 20, 1965
  - Item 12: Proposals in AFL-CIO Report Called Incredibly Timid and Puny, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Howard Taubman
    Notes: 3/28/1967
  - Item 13: Does Meany Speak for the Rank and File?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Ralph de Toledano
    Notes: Right-to-Work Committee Report
  - Item 14: Does Meany Speak for the Rank and File?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Right-to-Work Committee Report; copy 2
  - Item 15: Conference Celebration, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5 June 1971. Original news clipping.
  - Item 16: The Hands that Build America, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: New York Times
    Notes: November 17, 1963
  - Item 17: Negro Loses State AFL-CIO Post, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 11/3/1967
  - Item 18: Feud Marks Eve of State Labor Parley, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: George Bliss
    Notes: 9/25/1967
  - Item 19: Senate Kills Labor Unit Vote Fund Ban, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Philip Warden
    Notes: 9/12/1967
  - Item 20: Iron Grip Harder to Maintain, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 10/5/1967. Guest Editorial.
  - Item 21: AFL-CIO Political Fund Dinner Nov. 7, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Robert M. Lewin
    Notes: 10/4/1967
  - Item 22: 2 Cabinet Aids at Labor's Parley, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Associated Press
    Notes: 12/7/1967
  - Item 23: Meany Rips Reuther, War Foes, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Chicago Tribune
    Notes: 12/8/1967
  - Item 24: Meany Beaming: AFL-CIO Meets on Happy Note, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Meany Tells AFL-CIO: No Union Fights Alone, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12/12/1967
  - Item 26: Will Reuther Tackle the Revived Meany?, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Don Harris
    Notes: 12/23/1967
  - Item 27: AFL-CIO Delegates Cite Gains, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12/4/1967
  - Item 28: AFL-CIO Elects George Meany to 6th 2-Year Term, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12/14/1965
  - Item 29: Meany Hits White House Pay Guidelines, Calls Them First Step to Federal Control, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Wall Street Journal
    Notes: 3/27/1964
  - Item 30: Meany Censures Johnson on Pay, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: David R. Jones
  - Item 31: Meany Opposes Johnson on U.S. Wage Guidelines, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Joel Seldin
  - Item 32: Meany Deplores U.S. Joblessness, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Stanley Levey
    Notes: 4/5/1963
  - Item 33: Johnson Wage-Price Guides Hit by Meany, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Meany Rejects the Guidelines, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Chicago Daily News
    Notes: 3/30/1964
  - Item 35: AFL-CIO Rejects Wage Guidelines, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5/20/1964
  - Item 36: AFL-CIO Rejects Johnson's 'Guideposts' Seeking Wage Restraints in Contract Talks, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Jersey Labor Split by Power Struggle, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 6/16/1964
  - Item 38: Labor Plans on U.S. Funds, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12/16/1965
  - Item 39: AFL-CIO Zeroes in on Southern California, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Business Week
    Notes: 9/1/1962
  - Item 40: Politics to Occupy AFL-CIO Council Here, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: D.J.R. Bruckner
    Notes: 8/3/1964
  - Item 41: Local AFL-CIO Rips BGS's Stand on City Pay Scales, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 10/1/1964
  - Item 42: Industry Piling Up Too Much Cash: AFL-CIO, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1/7/1965
  - Item 43: Union Chiefs Gird to Fight Pay Charges, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 9/26/1964
  - Item 44: Excerpts from Speech by Peter Henle, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Peter Henle
    Notes: 7/18/1957
  - Item 45: United We Stand, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Horace Brock
    Notes: 6/17/1964. AFL-CIO Advertisment and attached letter.
  - Item 46: Labor's 'Big Challenge': Unorganized Areas Show Job Pickup, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 11/17/1962
  - Item 47: Labor's Policies Defended, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 3/16/1962
  - Item 48: Lessons for Labor: AFL-CIO Alters Approach as Drive for Members Lags, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Lawrence Lynch
    Notes: 3/16/1964
  - Item 49: AFL-CIO Promotes Ex-Communist Chief, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12/22/1963
  - Item 50: Management Ass. Told 35-Hr. Week is 'Hoax' on Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 2/14/1963
  - Item 51: Power but No Push, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 11/23/1963
  - Item 52: No Executive Unit Seen as Reuther Blow, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 53: Pious Nonsense at Miami Beach, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 12/14/1967
  - Item 54: AFL-CIO Invites Hubert to Speak, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Chicago American
    Notes: 9/4/1967
  - Item 55: Labor Parley Snubs Dirksen and Percy, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 9/6/1967
  - Item 56: Kirkland Feels Heat to Quit: AFL-CIO Boss Refuses to Budge, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Stephen Franklin
    Notes: 2/26/1995
  - Item 57: Services for the Unemployed, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 58: Remarks Prepared for Delivery by Ray Marshall before 32nd AFL-CIO Union-Industries Show, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5/6/1977
  - Item 59: The Pocketbook Issues: AFL-CIO Recommendations for 1992, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 60: The Pocketbook Issues: AFL-CIO Policy Recommendations for 1992, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: copy 2
  - Item 61: The Permanent Replacement of Workers Striking Over Health Care Benefits in 1990, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Department of Employee Benefits
    Notes: June 1991
- AFL-CIO 4th Constitutional Convention, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  books
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the AFL-CIO 4th Constitutional Convention: Volume 1 Daily Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: 12/7/1961-12/13/1961
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the AFL-CIO 4th Constitutional Convention: Volume 1 Executive Council Reports, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report of the AFL-CIO Executive Council: Seventh Convention, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Presidential Campaigns, 1960-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The AFL-CIO Platform Proposals, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The AFL-CIO Platform Proposals, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The Making of a Campaign Issue: Nixon at the AFL-CIO Convention, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The AFL-CIO Platform Proposals, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Platform Proposals of the AFL-CIO to the Republican and Democratic National Conventions 1964, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Congress, 1973-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Legislative reports
  - Item 1: Labor Looks at the 94th Congress, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: AFL-CIO Department of Legislation
    Notes: AFL-CIO Legislative Report
  - Item 2: Labor Looks at the 93rd Congress, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The People's Lobby: AFL-CIO Report on the 98th Congress 1983-84, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor Looks at Congress 1973, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: Legislative Report
  - Item 5: The People's Lobby: An AFL-CIO Report on the 97th Congress, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AIDS, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  pamphlets and brochures
  - Item 1: Why You Should be Informed about AIDS, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Family's Guide to AIDS: Responding with Your Heart, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Michael Helquist
  - Item 3: Coping with AIDS, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Medical Answers About AIDS, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Lawrence Mass
  - Item 5: AIDS: The Emerging Ethical Dilemmas, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Surgeon General's Report on Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Your Child and AIDS, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: AIDS in the Workplace: A Supervisory Guide, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: AIDS and Your Job- Are There Risks?, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Coping with AIDS: Psychological and Social Considerations in Helping People with HTLV-III Infection, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: AIDS Medical Guide, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Linda Maxey and Gayling Gee
  - Item 12: Coping with ARC, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Buck Nunes and Chuck Frutchey
  - Item 13: Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome: 100 Questions and Answers, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: 1/1/1986
- AIDS, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Caring for Someone with AIDS, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: AIDS: Dilemma in the Workplace, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Recommendations for Preventing Transmission of Human Immunodeficiency Virus and Hepatitis B Virus to Patients During Exposure-Prone Invasive Procedures, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Center for Disease Control
    Notes: 7/12/1991
  - Item 4: Protection Against Occupational Exposure to Hepatitis B Virus (HBV) and Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV), 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: 10/19/1987
  - Item 5: Recommendations for Prevention of HIV Transmission in Health-Care Settings, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: 8/21/1987
  - Item 6: American Corporate Policy: AIDS and Employment, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Guidelines for the Handling and Treatment of Medical/Infectious Waste, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Understanding AIDS, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Surgeon General
- Absenteeism, 1952-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: How to Cut Absenteeism, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Absenteeism and Lateness, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: What About Women's Absenteeism and Labor Turnover?, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Age Discrimination, 1956-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  pamphlets
  - Item 1: 1978 Age Discrimination Act Amendments, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: 1978 Age Discrimination Act Amendments, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Law Against Age Discrimination in Employment, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The Law Against Age Discrimination in Employment, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Age Discrimination in Employment Act of 1967 with Explanation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Captain of a Mighty Host: A Note on the Retirement of John L. Lewis, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: John Hutchinson
  - Item 7: Job Performance and Age: A Study in Measurement, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Apprenticeship, 1955-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Standards with Schedules of Work Processes and Related Instructions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: UWA Skilled Trades Department
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship and CETA, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Apprenticeship Past and Present, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Reginald Perry
- Arbitration, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report of Committee on Ethics on Standards of Conduct for Labor Arbitrators, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: 1/14/1949
  - Item 2: Procedural and Substantive Aspects of Labor-Management Arbitration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Process of Arbitration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Abraham A. Diamond
- Arbitration, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Bar, Bench, and Table: An Arbitral Drama, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Alfred B. Carb and Albert I. Edelman
  - Item 2: "Ask Any Fair-Minded Man", Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: The Arbitration of Discharge Cases: What Happens After Reinstatement, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Arthur M. Ross
- Arbitration, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  pamphlets, news clippings
  - Item 1: Arbitration for Buyers and Sellers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Guidelines for Arbitration Witnesses: Suggestions for the Witness in Appearing at an Arbitration Hearing, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Clarence M. Updegraff
  - Item 3: Arbitration in the Public Sector, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Robert G. Howlett
  - Item 4: Preparation for Arbitration and Hearing Procedure: A Summary of Advice and Information for Company and Union Representatives, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Model Arbitration Clauses to Protect Management Rights, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: A Supreme Court Justice Looks at Arbitration, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Arthur J. Goldberg
    Notes: 3/17/1965
  - Item 7: What's Wrong with Labor Arbitration?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: F.A. O'Connell
  - Item 8: Resistance to Grievance Arbitration, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Richard Martin Lyon
  - Item 9: Labor Arbitration: Procedures and Techniques, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Arbitration in Illinois- Need for Change, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Andre M. Saltoun and Bruce J. McWhirter
    Notes: January 1961
  - Item 11: Hotta Attacks Arbitration Bill; Says Jails Would be Swamped, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Felix Belair Jr.
    Notes: 5/2/1963
  - Item 12: Railroads Urge a Ban on Strikes, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: 4/10/1963
  - Item 13: On Arbitration: Critics Feel It Violates Basic Freedoms and Doesn't Work, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Joseph A. Loftus
    Notes: 7/14/1963
  - Item 14: A Review of Arbitration in Labor Contracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Howard Jensen
- Arbitration, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Evidence & Proof in Arbitration, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Martin F. Scheinman
  - Item 2: Judicial and Administrative Deference to Arbitration, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Benjamin Aaron
  - Item 3: The Coming End of Arbitration's Golden Age, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: David E. Feller
  - Item 4: The Impact of External Law Upon Labor Arbitration, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Arbitration as a Substitute for Other Legal Remedies, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Harold W. Davey
  - Item 6: Analysis of Michigan Experience with Last Offer Compulsory Arbitration of Police and Fire Labor Disputes, 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Eugene F. Berrodin and Raymond Jones
    Notes: 3/14/1979
- Arbitration, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Alternative Dispute Resolution and Enforcement of Statutory Rights, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: James R. LaVaute
    Notes: 8/9/1989
  - Item 2: An Experiment in the Mediation of Grievances, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Stephen B. Goldberg and Jeanne M. Brett
  - Item 3: Decisional Thinking of Labor Arbitrators and Federal Judges as Triers of Fact, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Edgar A. Jones, Jr.
    Notes: 6/10/1980-6/13/1980
- Arbitration, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Six Principles of Neutrality and Fairness for Employment Dispute Resolution Practice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Arbitration Compulsory, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: Theodore W. Kheel, Esq.
  - Item 2: The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Compulsory Arbitration: Panacea or Millstone?, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: Harold S. Roberts
- Automation, 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Automation Management: The Social Perspective, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: Ellis L. Scott and Roger W. Bolz
  - Item 2: Implications of Automation and Other Technological Developments, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Autoworkers (UAW) General, 1963-1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Labor Looks at Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Solidarity House, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: 3/10/1965
  - Item 3: This Union Cause, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Solidarity House, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Autoworkers (UAW) Public Review Board, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A More Perfect Union, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Second Annual Report of the Public Review Board to the Membership of the UAW, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Democracy and Public Review: An Analysis of the UAW Public Review Board, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: Jack Stieber, Walter E. Oberer, and Michael Harrington
- Autoworkers (UAW) Collective Bargaining Convention, 1967-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Workers' Problems Are Democracy's Problems, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: 4/27- 4/29/1961
  - Item 2: UAW National Collective Bargaining Convention: Resolution-1979 Collective Bargaining Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: 4/17-4/18/1979
  - Item 3: Special Collective Bargaining Convention Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: 4/27-4/29/1961
- Autoworkers (UAW) 15th Constitutional Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Report of Walter P. Reuther to the 15th Constitutional Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther
    Notes: 3/27-4/1/1955
- Autoworkers (UAW) Constitutional Convention, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Special Constitutional Convention Proceedings, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: 1/22-1/24/1958
- Autoworkers (UAW) 18th Constitutional Convention, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: 18th Constitutional Convention Proceedings, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: 5/4- 5/10/1962
- Autoworkers (UAW) 19th Constitutional Convention, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Report of President Walter P. Reuther to the 19th UAW Constitutional Convention, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: 3/20-3/27/1964; Part 2- Economic Conditions